Are you having a good time?
Blink Twice is a mystery, thriller film directed by Zoë Kravitz.
When tech billionaire Slater King meets cocktail waitress Frida at his fundraising gala, he
invites her to join him and his friends on a dream vacation on his private island.
But despite the epic setting, beautiful people, ever-flowing champagne, and late-night dance parties,
Frida can sense that there’s something sinister hiding beneath the island’s lush façade.
Frida, played by Naomi Ackie.
Slater, played by Channing Tatum.
Jess, played by Alia Shawkat.
Vic, played by Christian Slater.
Cody, played by Simon Rex.
Sarah, played by Adria Arjona.
Blink Twice is a 2024 American psychological thriller film directed and produced by Zoë
Kravitz (in her directorial debut) from a script she wrote with E.T.
Feigenbaum.
The film stars Naomi Ackie, Channing Tatum, Christian Slater, Simon Rex, Adria
Arjona, Haley Joel Osment, Kyle MacLachlan, Geena Davis, and Alia Shawkat.
It tells the story of a group of people invited to the private island of a billionaire
tech mogul as something strange and sinister happens with the attendees.
Blink Twice premiered at the DGA Theater in Los Angeles on August 8, 2024, and was released in the
United States on August 23 by Amazon MGM Studios through Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures.
The film grossed $48 million worldwide on a $20 million production
budget, and received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of rape, forgiveness,
exploitation, dark comedy, seclusion.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.